SURELY TOMORROW
I went all the way there. Was she
flirting with me or threatening me?
She's the one who's confused, not me.
Why bring luggage when you're flirting?
That's my plan. Mind your own business.
If you have anything to say to Ji-woo,
do it later, during the daytime in a cafe.
Hey, Ji-woo,
don't you think this is outrageous?
-This man wrote about your husband--
-Ex-husband.
And you're with him
in the middle of the night--
The evening.
Jeez, hey… Look.
You're not speaking the facts.
Oh, so the fact is you're flirting
by living together?
I have no reason to explain it.
You need to leave.
Well, I need to eat gimbap. I'm busy.
Jesus…
Jin-eon, you need to leave.
-Hey.
-Don't "hey" her.
-Kyeong-do, you need to stop too.
-Okay.
I will not
let this situation slide.
Seo Ji-woo, this is wrong.
Understood?
Fine, sure, I'll leave. All right.
I'm leaving.
You haven't eaten, right? Eat.
Tuna gimbap is your favorite.
-Is it good?
-Do you want this?
You have ten minutes.
Chew fucking well and get the hell out.
I said, if you act like this,
you're confused too.
I'm not confused.
Going to the UK like this is not right.
It's irresponsible in this condition.
Besides, why cause harm
to the United Kingdom?
If you want to go,
quit drinking before you go.
What's with the luggage?
You were right.
To make you study, I should read with you.
To put you on a diet,
I should exercise with you.
Instead of yelling at you to quit,
I plan to take care of you by your side.
I've been in AA programs.
Are you going to live here?
You know how cunning one can be?
Now that this is where I'm going to live,
it's nice.
You have a very nice house.
How many rooms do you have?
I have no room for you.
That's the master bedroom.
And that's the bathroom.
This is the dressing room.
Is that your study?
But you don't study. Is it for show?
Your dressing room must be huge.
The daughter of a clothing store owner.
Hey!
Cut it out and get out.
Cut what out? Then I'll use...
the master bedroom.
Are you kidding me?
Well, when you slept on my bed,
where did I sleep?
The couch, the sauna,
the sleeping room at my work.
My L5 and L6 still feel stiff.
I can't sleep on the couch.
-Do you want me to align your spine?
-So childish.
You're the one being childish.
You need to take responsibility
for what you do. You're old enough.
What have I done?
Look. You barged into my house
and stayed a few days, right?
And what did you say back then?
"To come to a house with someone waiting,
isn't it nice? Doesn't it feel warm?"
I've learned from it.
My brain remembers it.
Having another person in the house
couldn't be more comfortable. It's warm.
So I can't live alone anymore.
Is there a bathroom in the master bedroom?
I'm going to kill you.
Let's sleep together. The bed is big.
Gosh. He's nuts.
Get me some chamomile tea.
Make sure it's hot.
Kiss my ass. Jesus.
JI-YEON
SE-YEONG
Shit, is he crazy?
Jeez…
-Open the door.
-Tell me the door code.
Shut up and open the door,
or I'll call the police.
You can wire transfer it to my account.
Are you going to keep acting like a kid?
I get it, so open the door.
Would you do it if you were me?
Give me your ear.
-Why?
-Are you expecting me to say it out loud?
Hey!
You think you can get away from this?
-Hey!
-Open the door.
-Open the door or lose your ear.
-Let go!
Let it go! Hey.
Jeez, do you want to sleep outside?
Jesus, that hurts.
0917. Open the door now.
Send me a video
of you punching the passcode in.
Seriously, you're so evil.
This is my house.
And that was my house, you woman.
Forget it if you don't want to.
Okay, fine. Okay, I get it.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
Be reasonable and take a shower
in the guest bathroom.
No. You took a shower in my house too.
Because there was only one.
So? Are you showing off
that you have a big house?
Well, let me take a shower then.
Don't you dare. You little…
Gosh...
SURELY TOMORROW
EPISODE 5
You don't even have cereal.
If you eat so little and drink that much,
you won't last long.
Your bones will be brittle,
and you won't be able to walk.
If you change the door code by chance,
things will get fun.
Look forward to getting humiliated.
You heard me.
I bet you heard me.
Bye.
Hello, building manager?
What do I do to change the door code?
I've never tried it before.
You've been leaving work on time.
Do you have a side job?
It's not like I have left on time
that often.
Maybe I'm tired
because you're in the office.
Since when did you care about me?
Dongwoon Daily Entertainment Team.
Can I talk to Reporter Kim Doo-jin?
May I ask who's calling?
Who am I talking to?
I'm the Entertainment Team's
assistant manager.
Reporter Lee Kyeong-do? This is An Da-hye.
Hello.
It's the first time since the awards.
It's been years.
Right. Anyway, why do you want to talk
to Reporter Doo-jin?
I have something to ask,
but he won't answer his phone.
Is that so?
May I ask what it's about?
I'm getting a lot of thoughts in here.
I have way too much time.
I mean, as you know,
it's not like I'm a top celebrity
or a hot girl band member.
But following me for months
to release an article about my affair…
Isn't it unnatural?
So I was just curious.
Who on earth reported my private life?
We can't disclose the informant.
Right.
But it's strange.
I think there's more to this.
This wasn't even about me, but…
maybe…
I was the bait?
That's what occurred to me.
If you meet Reporter Kim Doo-jin,
tell him to pick up the phone.
Hey…
Who was it? Why look for Doo-jin?
I think it was Doo-jin's hater.
Just perfect.
Don't make ramyeon. Eat it with rice.
That looks good. Where's Dad?
We have more to dry clean than usual.
I have to go back, too.
I'll drop you off on the way then.
No, I'm going to vacuum the house
before I go.
Look.
An elder at church has a niece--
Mom,
do you think I can go on a blind date
when I'm going abroad?
His niece works in Chicago.
She's just old enough,
and she has a decent job.
Do you want me to live there forever?
I'm saying, his niece is dispatched there.
You can come back together later.
Do you want to see her picture?
I'll vacuum the house before I go.
My goodness…
OPEN
What? Really?
-Why are you filling the fridge?
-I need to eat.
I'm tired of talking to you.
When are you leaving?
Let's set the limit.
I'm making ramyeon. Want some?
I don't plan to eat with you.
Oh.
"Oh"?
Jeez.
Did I tell you that
my manager goes to my mom's laundromat
just to have her kimchi?
Was it 16 km? Gosh, 16 km from Seoul, wow…
Now you're even using kimchi to flirt?
Power on.
Gosh, are you crazy?
No, this kimchi is crazy.
When will you grow up?
Is this funny to you?
It is indeed. Do you want chopsticks?
When are you going to grow up?
Here.
Is it that good to eat in a rush?
-No.
-How's the kimchi?
Your mother made it?
All right. Let's go.
It's just you and me here.
-What are you doing?
-I tried to ignore it. But I just can't.
Hey, this is so sudden--
I can't do it alone.
Do what?
No, hey, no, what are you doing? No, hey!
I can't reach it.
What?
Shit. Oh, seriously!
Why are you getting nervous?
-Your face turned red.
-I'm not nervous, and it's not red.
Just sit down.
Oh, seriously.
Just breathe. You can't make abs
just by holding your breath.
Hey, this is pretty amazing.
Shut up.
Just to feed you,
I carried that kimchi container.
Jeez, hey, you got a muscle ache
just from carrying that?
Just get out.
Or is it the bed?
That 30 million won mattress?
Thirty million?
Okay, so where?
What? Oh, under the right shoulder joint.
Here?
No, go… higher.
A little more to the left.
Here?
What? Yes.
Your heart is fucking pounding.
Kyeong-do, are you turned on?
Yeah?
No. Shit.
Oh, this is hilarious.
You started it, but you fell for it.
Why is your heart beating so fast?
See? How dare you come at me?
Whatever. Let's go.
What?
I know exactly when you crave alcohol.
If you feel like drinking again,
let's take a walk outside. This is nice.
Tell a depressive
to take a walk 100 times.
If they have the will to walk outside,
they're not depressive.
You see how precious I am?
If someone like me tells you
to eat, rest, or walk,
you're at least forced to do it, you know?
I want to sit down. I'm tired.
We barely started.
How are you tired already?
Sit down.
Gosh.
Kyeong-do.
I'll leave when you become
a decent human being. Say no more.
If I'm not a human, am I an animal?
Alcohol.
Drinking...
is just too much.
I know it from experience.
It's very tough.
I don't drink that much.
That's how alcoholics begin.
They say they never drink enough
to be in danger.
To me, you're on the borderline.
If it gets any worse, you're in trouble.
It'll get ugly.
But I'm trying.
You need someone by your side
to stop drinking.
If you leave for England or anywhere,
what would you be doing by yourself?
Do you have family there or a friend?
You know you're running away.
About the alcoholism treatment…
Yes, ask away.
Do they tell you to be separated
from the person who upsets you?
Jeez, I'm craving alcohol.
No, they don't.
Hey, that 30 million won mattress
is not for me.
I'll sleep on the couch…
What?
Are you trying to put pressure on me?
Hold on.
Did you get breakfast for me?
My goodness.
I've never expected this
to happen in my life.
Thank you.
Is it good?
So good. This is delicious.
You see, I'm just leading you
down the garden path.
That's it.
Gosh, it's only the morning, but you…
If you come here again after work,
you're a dead man.
Keep that in mind.
Get me some milk tomorrow.
I prefer milk with my sandwich.
SEO JI-WOO
I took your stuff back to your house.
If you bring it back,
I'm calling the police.
She should've washed them
before packing up.
I said I'd meet you outside.
People here will see you--
Do you know what I received?
"Owen Kang" on this list is you, isn't it?
RYAN GOLD FOFS VIP INVESTMENT
LIST OF VICTIMS
Calm down. I'll explain it to you.
What's there to explain?
All those swindlers
vanished into thin air already.
I… I wondered
who'd fall for a fund like that.
How much did you invest?
Did you invest everything?
Don't worry. Once the company's sold,
I'll pay you first.
Hey, you think this tabloid
won't leak anytime soon?
How long do you think
you can hide it from your wife?
I don't plan to get married yet.
What?
What about you?
Are you doing this
because your family forced you?
That's what I want to know.
She's still my wife.
So I didn't want to show you this video.
I'm only revealing it to keep you calm.
I told you it'd be soon.
She wouldn't know if she's getting scammed
in that condition.
This is more torturous for me than you.
I lost that damn 30 billion won!
I've already talked to
Executive Director Choi.
When I told her to take MANZAAR,
she was happy about it.
Don't worry about the rest.
You just have to get a good price, okay?
Fine.
Gosh, this is crazy.
I said I'm calling the police
if you come back.
It's an errand.
What is it this time? Sashimi?
Se-yeong sent me.
Se-yeong?
Keep your shoes on. Just say it there.
Wait. There they are. My slippers.
Let's go.
Go where? Why?
Woo-sik's performing.
Se-yeong told me to bring you.
She hasn't told me.
So I'm here to tell you. Let's go.
Without a notice…
We have to leave now,
so we can eat before the play.
I'm sorry, but it's hard for me
to sit for a long time in a closed space.
I'll talk to Se-yeong later.
Have you had dinner?
Isn't it too early for dinner?
Since I'm here, we might as well go out.
For dinner and a walk.
That damn walk again… It's boring.
Boring?
How about an amusement park?
Crowded places exhaust me.
If it's a quiet one, would you go?
What? Are you going to rent
the whole place or something?
How did you know?
Are you really going nuts now?
You know what?
What if
I rent a whole amusement park
and take you there, what would you bet?
Oh… What should I bet?
Oh, you can start working at the company.
Fine. I'll start working at the company.
You will? Okay.
You… When you said
you were going to meet that fortuneteller,
I should've stopped you!
How frustrating.
You still believe
what that fortuneteller said…
How long do you plan to stay deceived?
My heart! It's hell!
You're really good at emotional acting.
Even better than Park Bo-gum.
I should've been
more good-looking than him.
Gosh, not even plastic surgery can do it.
Dude, I was just pretending.
I get why Ji-woo didn't come,
but Kyeong-do should've come to watch.
Anyway, Lee Kyeong-do's going nuts
after Seo Ji-woo appeared.
At least we get to drink makgeolli
because Kyeong-do isn't here.
Kyeong-do has come. Twice already.
Hey, by the way,
will it work out between Kyeong-do
and Ji-woo this time?
They should've worked it out
on your wedding day.
SUMMER, 2015
-Thank you.
-You look so pretty.
-Shall we go? We'll see you later.
-Yeah.
-Congratulations.
-Later.
Okay.
Ji-woo!
Come here. Sit.
When did you get back?
I can't believe I get to see you
get married. You look beautiful.
Are you here for my wedding? Really?
I thought you emailed me to invite me.
I had to see my family, too.
Welcome back. I'm so glad you're here.
You had to come. You're Chaos's manager.
Oh, my Ji-woo.
Everyone, please look behind.
The moment has arrived.
The bride and the groom will enter now.
Please celebrate
their bright future together
with your loudest cheers and applause.
Bride and groom, enter.
Seo Ji-woo.
Long time no see.
I heard you live in New York.
Yes.
Are you back for the wedding?
That and other stuff.
When are you going back?
Soon.
You've become a journalist.
Yes.
That's cool.
Bye.
Hey.
You should've told me.
You should've told me…
why you had to leave.
You should've said goodbye.
What was I supposed to say?
"I don't want to see you anymore.
Goodbye." Something like that?
Back then,
you were becoming sadder every day.
What more could I have done?
THANK YOU FOR MARRYING EACH OTHER
SORRY NOT SORRY
Bye!
Have fun! Call me when you get back!
Wait, Se-yeong.
Give me Seo Ji-woo's number.
Hey, you lunatic.
How can you seriously
stop me for this at my wedding?
Of course. Give me that.
Jesus.
Seriously, you two are hypocrites.
Why didn't you look for each other sooner?
Lee Kyeong-do, good luck.
Good luck.
-We're really leaving now.
-Bye!
Bye!
Have fun!
Hey, Seo Ji-woo.
Hey, Seo Ji-woo!
Yes.
Come out.
Fucking come out now!
What a drunkard.
Can a Dongwoon Daily journalist
be like this?
I'm an ace.
This wouldn't affect my position.
I already drank from that.
So what? Jesus fucking Christ.
You're…
good at swearing now.
Thanks to you.
Did you drink a lot? You're pretty drunk.
Because I'd kill you
if I met you in my right mind.
Well, even if I die, I'd have no regrets.
Shit…
Who cares if you die?
Tell me before you go.
Say something!
Let me know why at least, fuck. Shit…
Jeez.
Back then…
how did you feel, Kyeong-do?
How your diligent parents
looked different.
Your mother made 320,000 won
on a side job.
From working a whole month.
How it was only worth one shirt for me.
I know it broke your heart.
Shit.
You didn't really
have to explain that to anyone.
Just because a 20-year-old Lee Kyeong-do…
loved Seo Ji-woo the liar.
I knew it wouldn't be a one-time thing.
Your feelings will continue to be hurt,
and you'll be sad.
That's what I thought.
The 20-year-old me…
Well, I didn't know what to do.
I just thought…
I should no longer be with you.
I didn't know what else to do.
Fuck.
Hey…
The Kyeong-do who insisted
that we eat pork cutlet.
And you thought it was all your fault.
We were…
only 20 back then.
I'm hungry.
Me too.
I never expected
Woo-sik and Se-yeong to get married.
They were always fighting.
That made them grow on each other.
When are you leaving?
Today.
You'll have to go straight to work.
Come on. Let me get you a taxi.
Okay.
DONGWOON DAILY
Oh… I missed the flight.
Did you miss it because you overslept?
I missed it because I couldn't sleep.
Well, it's not that spacious.
Yeah, I see that.
Hey, people have
what's called an attitude.
"It's perfect for living alone.
It's cozy." There are many ways.
Is this the bathroom?
You still never listen.
When was the last time you cleaned it?
Pretty recently?
Why does your bathroom
smell like a public restroom?
Get a hotel.
I can't. If my mom finds out,
she'll check every hotel there is.
Then don't complain.
I was too naive to believe
that you'd be nice to me.
Get some rest.
There's nothing but water in the fridge.
Call me if you need anything.
Where are you going?
Well… To a sauna or a jjimjilbang.
Are you telling me to stay alone?
I'll just go to a jjimjilbang instead.
Or get a motel…
You and your temper.
I'm going to the supermarket
to get some bathroom cleaner.
UNDERPASS SHOP
Hello. Is this…
Here.
-How much is it?
-25,000 won.
-25,000 won? Bye.
-Bye.
Do you have a toothbrush…
DONGWOON DAILY
SEOUL IS HOSTING
'2015 SEOUL CULTURE WEEK'
Oh, wow.
That's new. The cursor has been blinking
for an hour now.
I think I'll need more information on it.
That's also new.
I've been too complacent lately.
Let me do some legwork.
Here.
Home, please.
What?
I mean Yeonnam-dong, please.
Have you had lunch?
Where are you?
-The laundry.
-The lau…
You should've told me.
WASHER
You're really early.
Are you doing the laundry?
But there's a washer at home.
Just to get some fresh air.
I have ten minutes left.
Okay.
Anyway, why are you back so early?
I was done early.
I thought you'd be bored, so I rushed.
Cool.
Yes.
I've been cool since 2007.
Only you didn't know.
Let's get to know each other.
What did you do in New York?
I've been going to school for too long.
I was already in a doctoral program
before I knew.
What's your major?
Aesthetics.
I had nothing else to do.
So I just studied.
You'll still get the degree, right?
Are you telling me to go back?
What?
Oh, no. I'm saying--
Fucking condescending
for letting me sleep for a night.
No, what I mean is--
I'm not leaving.
When I went to your company with my stuff,
I'd made my decision.
At least I had.
It's your turn now.
Gosh.
Why did I leave too early?
What if I get fired?
Let me… provide for you.
Let's listen to a song.
What song?
I just love this song so much.
What's wrong? What is it?
Have you done it before?
Done what?
Well, it's not my first time.
So have you done it before?
What do you mean?
Oh… Jeez, just go to sleep.
-What is it?
-Sleep.
What is it?
Oh, just go to sleep.
-What is it?
-I… Oh!
Okay.
JI-WOO KYEONG-DO
PUBLIC BATHHOUSE
-Hey.
-Yeah?
-What's this?
-What?
-Why do you still--
-Give me that.
-Give it to me.
-Why did you take it out?
-Let me see.
-No.
Please, let me see. Oh, no! No. Let me--
-Oh, pick it up. That's…
Hey, let's just go home. What is this?
Just wait. Why are you so hasty?
Yes, sir. Yes.
FOO LAND
Well, did you think I couldn't do it?
This amusement park looks like you.
It's bright and cute.
Bright?
You'd better get ready to go to work.
I want to work here.
Hey, Reporter Lee.
You never open at night.
Why do you charge me so much
when you don't open?
Who says I don't open at night?
Sometimes I do!
Normally, when I'm in good condition
and open at night like tonight,
I have at least 12 people. Always.
Based on my data so far.
But you're only paying for ten people.
What's in it for me then?
It's not even enough for the electricity.
I feel like you're ripping me off.
Never.
After I pay for the power,
I'm left with nothing.
This is basically
the culture contribution business.
Come on. Thanks to your article,
things worked out with the city hall,
and I get to run the business.
So I only get the money for the power
and contribute to the culture,
and your love business.
You're doing us a favor.
I lost count of
how many couples got married this way.
You probably lost count of
how much you ripped off. I sent it.
Watch your mouth.
All right. What do you want to ride first?
-That one.
-That one? Sounds good. Let's go.
-So? I rented the whole place.
-Oh, I love it.
-Enjoy it.
-Oh, yeah.
Thanks!
Sure!
Here we go.
Wow. Oh. Hey, come here!
Sir! One more time!
Okay!
Sir, please stop!
What do you mean?
So, what I'm saying
is that you didn't defend me well
during my divorce suit.
You know what it's like
when drugs are involved.
I've explained it enough--
No, what I'm saying is…
Shit…
So what I'm saying is,
we fell for the trap. You know?
Seo Ji-woo and that asshole
had set it up all along.
So they can get rid of me
and fucking stay together.
So they leaked… my drug use.
Which asshole?
Oh, fuck!
Dongwoon Daily
Entertainment Team's Lee Kyeong-do.
The one who wrote the article.
They're living together now.
Lawyer Park,
so my request today is,
can you overturn this divorce?
You must overturn it, okay?
Bring Seo Ji-woo back.
Sir, get us a ladder at least
so we can get down.
I can fix it soon. Just wait. Jesus.
Shit.
Stop making a fuss.
Not even children would be scared.
How is he checking the facility?
Aren't you scared?
No, it's relaxing.
It's rather comfortable.
I always knew you were weird.
It's not like I scheduled it.
No one is responsible for this time.
I'm tied down without a choice
in this moment and space.
It's not your fault or my fault.
So it's relaxing.
We're stuck anyway.
I rented the whole place.
You have to go to work now.
Keep your promise.
Okay.
Oh, the wind feels nice.
I mean, I think it's faster than expected.
It's nice because it's fast.
I think this is too fast.
You're so scared for real.
Wait. I know this song.
This is similar to a movie soundtrack.
It's not similar. This is the soundtrack.
I liked the lyrics,
so I wrote a column about it.
Dang.
How long
will I...
love you?
SURELY TOMORROW
Seo Ji-woo?
Long time no see…
Oh, hey.
Well, if you're here, why not go in?
Oh, say hi for me. I don't feel like…
Meet Kyeong-do before you go.
You've become handsome.
Bye.
What?
No, see Se-yeong before you go, okay?
Go on.
Come on.
See you later.
Ji-woo!
Kyeong-do, where are you?
Why are you so late, you idiot? Hurry up.
Jesus, you're so late.
-Kyeong-do's fatal first love…
-Have you seen my clothes?
-…stopped Seo Ji-woo.
-Jeez.
You wear them.
Are you friends
or are you in a relationship again?
I don't want us to be just friends.
What do you have to tell me?
Is it about that?
You're not going to Chicago?
What does she mean to you
that you surrender every time?
Good job, Seo Ji-woo.
Thank you for surviving.
I was doing just fine
and suddenly showed up divorced.
Why are you still so stupid?
Did you cry a lot?
There's something I have to do.
If I don't get this sorted out now,
I'll be messed up for the rest of my life.